preparewise.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy

At PrepareWise, LLC (“PrepareWise”), we take special care to protect the information you provide to us because we value your business, and your trust. By visiting Preparewise.com you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy Notice.

#### Personal Information

When you create an account or place an order on PrepareWise’s website, the information gathered is for the sole use of PrepareWise. The information collected may include, but is not necessarily limited to, your name and the name of any recipient of products purchased by you on the website; your address and the address of any recipient of products purchased by you on the website; your phone number and that of any recipient of products purchased by you on the website; your E-mail address; and your payment processing information, such as credit card numbers and billing addresses.

#### Disclosure of Personal Information

Our goal is to limit sharing your personal information to those instances where it is necessary in processing a transaction through a third party which completes a billing payment, or performs a service on behalf of PrepareWise. PrepareWise will never sell, trade, or transfer your personal information to parties not authorized by you or required for the completion of the transaction, or unless compelled to do so by order of a governmental agency in the exercise of its legitimate governmental authority.We will use all reasonable means to prevent unauthorized access to your personal information, and to maintain the accuracy and appropriate use thereof.

#### Children’s Information

PrepareWise does not collect or maintain information from those it actually knows are under the age of 18, and will not accept orders from persons it knows are under the age of 18.

#### Uses of Your Personal Information

The information obtained by PrepareWise is used safely and securely to complete your transaction and to enhance the service PrepareWise provides to you. It will be used to expand personalization efforts, as well as to: activate your PrepareWise account; deliver products and update you on transaction information; process and deliver contest entries and prizes; help PrepareWise to improve its website and its customer service; and, unless you advise us otherwise in writing, to send notifications to you regarding products, offers, promotions, news, or other events.

#### Cookies and IP Addresses

PrepareWise uses cookies to help enhance and personalize your food storage shopping experience. They allow PrepareWise to recognize your browser and to help identify you once you return to the website, so that information from prior visits can be recalled. The ability to accept or decline the use of cookies can be controlled through your personal computer. However, components of the personalization at preparewise.com will not be maintained once cookies are disabled on your computer.

#### Changes to this Policy

PrepareWise may periodically make changes to this Policy. Updates will be reflected by the date under the “Last Modified” heading at the top of this page.

#### Contact Us

If you have questions, concerns, or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact a customer service representative at 1.888.545.6265 or send an E-mail to privacy@preparewise.com. You may also direct your questions, comments, and concerns to the following address:

  * PrepareWise, LLC
  * 510 South 200 West, Suite 200
  * Salt Lake City, UT 84101
  * U.S.A.
  * Attn: Privacy
